atlanticdrugs.com 2011-09-03

# AtlanticDrugs - Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment** | 

AtlanticDrugs.com believes, recognizes, and values your right to privacy and confidentiality and is 100% committed to ensuring the highest standards of both. For this reason we provide ease of access to this privacy policy on our homepage and on all available pages so that it is readily available to be reviewed at any point.

To achieve the high standards we set ourselves; we use the latest in online security technology to ensure that your online security is not compromised. Including implementing appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures and processes to safeguard the important and confidential information you provide.

**How We Protect Your Confidential Information**

AtlanticDrugs.com uses Verisign as well as McAfee security and scans to ensure that any and all information you may provide during the time you use us as an internet facilitator, is kept confidential and secure from third-parties or outside agents.

This means that your secure information will be kept from loss, misuse, and any illegal alteration. Such protection is naturally vital in areas such as the checkout and payment procedure.

AtlanticDrugs.com is also Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPPA)-compliant. The Administrative Simplification provisions of 1996 (HIPAA, Title II) required the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS) to establish national standards for electronic health care transactions and national identifiers for providers, health plans and employers. We are committed to always maintaining this compliancy. 

|   
---|---  
**Information We Gather**

We collect personal information when you communicate with us by email or when you provide any information about yourself on any form on our website. This includes inquiries or the start of a medical processing service with a doctor. As a result of these actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, email address, phone number, address, and any other personal information that you choose to share with us. These will usually include some form of:

  * Contact Information
  * Medical History and Information
  * Billing Information

At any and all times this information is available to you to edit or change as per required. We have a special member’s area where this can be done easily, and once again, securely. 

**Our Guarantee**

AtlanticDrugs.com guarantees the privacy of this information and will under no circumstances release this information to any third party without your written consent for the same. 

All secure information and data collected will be limited to the minimum necessary to improve delivery and development of our services and other opportunities. All such personal information collected will be held securely in accordance with the law and the internal privacy policy of AtlanticDrugs. 

**Patient Responsibility**

By using AtlanticDrugs.com as an internet facilitator, you agree that it is your responsibility to: control the dissemination and use of activation codes and passwords. 

  * Authorize, monitor and control access to, and use of, your AtlanticDrugs account and password.
  * Promptly inform AtlanticDrugs of any need to deactivate a password.

**Consent**

By registering on the website and placing an order, you are accepting this Agreement and granting explicit permission to AtlanticDrugs to collect data including your sensitive personal data. 

**Important**

These privacy guidelines are communicated to all employees of AtlanticDrugs to ensure complete security and confidentiality of all personal information collected. 

You may visit and use AtlanticDrugs with the understanding that any dispute over privacy is governed by this Privacy Policy and the State Laws of Arizona. 

There may be links to certain other websites on the AtlanticDrugs website. This however does not mean that AtlanticDrugs endorses those websites. AtlanticDrugs does not share your personal information with these websites and is in no way responsible for the privacy policies of these websites. 

Users are encouraged to check and understand the privacy policies of individual websites and/or promoting companies before entering into any transactions with them. This Privacy Policy applies solely to AtlanticDrugs and does not cover any linked websites. 

This Privacy Policy is subject to change and applies only to information collected from you for your use of the website. Any changes in the Privacy Policy will be highlighted through a notice on the home page of AtlanticDrugs urging users to check this Privacy Policy statement. Your continued use of the website indicates your agreement with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
